Title: Memory of water - Luc Montagnier
Date: 11/19/2018
Modified: 11/19/2018
Category: Science
Tags: Science, Virology, Quantum Physics, Quantum Biology
Slug: memory-of-water-montagnier
Authors: Ramana M
Summary: Water holds memory and transmits them electromagnetically and is an experimental therapy.

**Explore topic - Memory of Water - Luc Montagnier**

Scientist : Luc Montagnier

Source: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Luc_Montagnier

Nobel price winning scientist Luc Montagnier and Robert Gallo discussed the AIDS Human Immuno-deficiency Virus(HIV).

In 2009, Montagnier published two independently-made, controversial research studies, one of which was entitled "Electromagnetic Signals Are Produced by Aqueous Nanostructures Derived from Bacterial DNA Sequences." It has been said that, if its conclusions are true, "these would be the most significant experiments performed in the past 90 years, demanding re-evaluation of the whole conceptual framework of modern chemistry".[4] The paper concludes that diluted DNA from pathogenic bacterial and viral species is able to emit specific radio waves" and that "these radio waves [are] associated with ‘nanostructures’ in the solution that might be able to recreate the pathogen".

We find that with DNA, we cannot work at the extremely high dilutions used in homeopathy; we cannot go further than a 10−18 dilution, or we lose the signal. But even at 10−18, you can calculate that there is not a single molecule of DNA left. And yet we detect a signal.

Papers:
Electromagnetic Signals Are Produced by Aqueous Nanostructures Derived from Bacterial DNA Sequences
https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/20640822



